(Birds singing)
GEORGE: You have to understand,
we've had so many weirdos
who just want to come in
and see this place up close.
So, I need to check
on a few things,
and I'll be right back.
There is no way we pull this off.
Okay, we look like
the worst possible versions
of Heidi Klum and Seal.
Do you ever stop complaining?
I have a right to complain.
Okay, the council
sent me here because
they obviously think
I'm expendable.
And I had to put khakis on,
so it's been a hard day
for all of us.
So maybe just shut up.
GEORGE: All right,
Mr. and Mrs. James.
(Chuckles)
The wire transfer went through.
All you need to do now is sign.
I just can't wait to start
making babies in our new home.
(Chuckles)
Well, before you start that,
there, there are issues
I legally have to make you aware of.
This house has been unoccupied
for quite some time.
Over the past decade alone,
there have been
an unprecedented amount
of break-ins,
missing persons reports.
And, of course,
the most disturbing...
You mean the people
that died there?
Yeah, we know.
About all 36 of them?
Uh, what can we say? (Laughs)
The wife's a sucker
for a farmhouse kitchen.
Okay, but to be clear,
we're not legally liable
for any accidents, fatal or otherwise.
Other than that,
congrats on your new home.
Yay.
Don't worry, we'll burn some sage.
(All laugh)
What. A. Shithole.
Oh, so you an obstinate house.
Just use the key.
(Lock clicks)
(Door creaking)
Weird.
How long did the realtor say
this place has been empty?
It looks like someone
still lives here.
Something definitely
lives here.
The psychic energy is stronger than
anything I've ever felt before.
This is not a home,
this is a prison.
I pity the souls trapped here.
It must be hell.
I've actually been to Hell.
I promise you, this is better.
Well, I'm sensing
really bad vibes.
Maybe we should go clubbing.
(Sighs) If you'd asked me
a few years ago,
I'd be hitting up
my coke dealer right now.
But I got a second chance
at life.
A third chance, actually.
I can't fuck it up.
Don't forget who gave you
that chance.
Do you honestly think
Michael is evil?
That's what we're here
to find out.
Cordelia wouldn't send us
all this way for no reason.
I've never seen
this spell before.
These spirits do not want
to be seen by us.
We are trespassers
in their home,
and if we want to talk to them,
we're gonna have
to force them out of hiding.
Boy Supreme's family died here.
If anyone has the goods
on Michael, it's them.
It's the others
I'm worried about.
This place is more crowded
than a French youth hostel.
Who knows what we're walking into?
Okay... let's see if this works.
My powers have been off since
we stepped into this place.
Monstra te spirituum.
BOTH:
Ne abscondas.
Ne abscondas!
Floor creaking)
Did it work?
We're in.
(Children's laughter echoing)
(Gasps)
Calm down, skinny witch.
(Laughing)
What the fuck happened
in this house?
TATE: I've told you this
a million times.
You're my psychiatrist.
You're supposed to help me.
BEN: I have helped you.
We've had daily sessions
going on for years now.
I feel like the only reason
you're talking to me
is 'cause your wife refuses
to talk to you.
Let's leave her out of this.
Well, then let's talk
about your daughter.
'Cause that's what I really
need your help with.
♪ Sometimes I feel
I've got to run away ♪
Violet, please, talk to me.
♪ Get away from the pain
that you drive ♪
You're the only thing I need!
It's torture.
Can you just talk to her?
What do you want me to say?
You set fire
to your mom's boyfriend,
you shot and killed over
a dozen kids in high school,
you helped kill her parents,
plus, you impregnated
her mother.
Any one of those things
would be reason enough...
I'm different now.
Yeah, I'm...
You know, I'm dead
and-and-and I'm hot,
and I know she has
feelings for me.
You're not so hot.
That's right, you can see us,
and we can see you.
Who are you?
I'm Behold Chablis.
This is Madison Montgomery.
You are Ben Harmon.
You killed yourself
in this house several years ago
after your wife died
in childbirth.
What are you talking about?
I didn't kill myself.
I was murdered.
What the fuck is going on here?
We decide when we want
to be seen.
Not anymore.
You're looking
at two powerful witches.
And the spell we cast is
just a small demonstration
of what we can do.
So, if you don't want
any more disruptions,
you're gonna have to answer
some hard questions
about Michael Langdon.
What are you gonna do,
make us more dead?
Even people protected by magic
aren't safe in this house.
I'd watch my ass if I were you.
(Sighs)
Look, it's really important.
Our coven bought you
a goddamn house
so nobody will come
to bother you ever again.
Sorry, you got me
at a bad time, I'm busy.
You're dead.
What do you have to do?
I got to look out the window
and cry while I masturbate.
It's my daily thing.
Okay, I know it's weird,
but I kind of feel for the guy.
Should we try to help him?
You mean the tear jerker?
Ew, no, the other guy.
Sounds like he's stuck
in a nightmare,
trapped in this Amityville reject
with the one thing he loves
but can never have.
It's a romantic tragedy.
(Screams)
Aah, get the fuck off of me!
- Be gone!
- You don't want to do that.
You'll have a house full
of spirits coming after you,
and they aren't all
as gentle as this one.
Beau, sweetie, you want to play?
Play!
Who the hell are you?
A friend of the house
and its residents.
They don't take kindly
to strangers.
You ain't dead?
Oh, honey,
I'm one of the few live ones
they let come and go.
And you are Madison Montgomery.
Oh, have you seen my movies?
- I have fans everywhere.
- No.
I've known a few Montgomerys
in my time,
but it's not every day
that I see a witch.
What are you?
Billie Dean Howard,
medium to the stars.
So, you're like
a shitty Ms. Cleo.
Excuse me?
Now, who do you think you are,
coming in here,
swanning around,
spewing vulgarities?
We're the new owners.
Who are you?
I'm Constance Langdon.
And this... is my fucking house.
(Chuckles)
Well, you two are
the most unlikely pair.
But, on the plus side,
your spawn will have
beautiful skin.
They're witches, Constance.
It's magic,
not marriage, that connects them.
They won't be moving in.
Well, now,
that is disappointing.
I guess I can't expect you
to go running down to the Korean
to get me my Crown Royal
and Virginia Slims?
You drink Crown Royal?
You're dead.
(Both chuckle)
It's true that this side
of the mortal coil
makes it impossible
to get a good buzz going,
but, well, old habits die hard.
(Woman clears throat)
It's done.
As demanded, the living room
has been tidied yet again.
We'll see about that.
I won't be but a moment.
It'll be more than a moment.
Oh.
(Chuckles)
Do you know what this is
on the tip of my finger?
It appears to be some dust
that I missed.
No, it's my sense of wonder.
Why, it-it's the color
of my piqued curiosity, it...
Oh, will you just
get on with it?
Just because we're
trapped here for eternity
doesn't mean you have to jabber
on forever to make a point.
Tell me, little Miss Moira,
if you're going to be
an old maid for all eternity,
why not be a decent one, hmm?
(Laughs) My real work,
my avocation, if you will,
isn't dusting...
it's satisfying your husband
in the basement.
Be careful.
My mother told me
pettiness causes wrinkles.
So does cruelty.
Disappointment makes
a woman bitter.
And when I think of all
of the unfulfilled dreams
that you left behind when
you took the coward's way out,
well, I guess I'd be pretty
miffed at the world, too.
You ladies all right in here?
It is so hard to find good help.
That poor woman.
In a house filled with tragedy,
she might be
the saddest soul of all.
- Oh, shut up.
- All right.
Look, we need the hot goss
on a guy who used to live here,
uh, Michael Langdon.
We have nothing to say
about him.
You did raise him, correct?
I said we're not talking.
Oh, pipe down, Billie.
I know more about that boy
than any woman, dead or alive.
But I don't spill a drop of tea
for free, kiddos.
Self-interest, hmm.
That's something I can get behind.
What do you want?
To remove that insufferable
cloudy-eyed ginger
from these premises permanently.
You want us to fire the help?
Well, if you really do have
witchcraft at your disposal,
then why don't you just
abracadabra that goddamn bitch
out of my afterlife, huh?
Bless me with some peace and quiet.
And then we can talk
about Michael all you want.
Got something!
Ah!
Nope.
Not hers.
It's got a totally
different vibration.
Moira's bones would be
much more morose.
You know this
is ridiculous, right?
This place has more bodies buried
than the catacombs in Rome.
If Constance wants us
to get rid of the maid,
I know a spell that can
easily bind her to the closet.
She'll never have
to see her again.
Keep digging.
Ah!
You have an enemy.
I'm proud to say I have many.
You can't live with virtue
without getting on the bad side
of those without.
Constance hates your guts.
She won't talk to us
unless we put you away.
Out of sight forever.
What are you going to do to me?
(Gasps)
Oh, heavens be.
My bones.
I can't begin to thank you.
These bones are my means
to escape.
Oh, thank you, thank you,
thank you.
(Whispering) Thank you. Thank you.
Okay.
Okay, you're getting slobber
on my clothes.
- (Sniffs, clears throat)
- Moira.
You have a choice.
Where do you want to be buried?
There's only one place
I've ever wanted to be.
How original,
to be buried in a cemetery.
Her wish was to be close
to her mother.
I want my bones to be buried
at the studio.
Paramount, Stage 7.
I would gladly haunt the shit
out of that place.
It's where they made me do
my first nude scene.
Totally gratuitous.
I begged for a body double,
but the asshole producer wanted
to get his rocks off, so...
You surprised me.
Under the facade
of a heartless narcissist...
Is a stone-cold bitch.
Listen, warlock,
I wouldn't think twice
about slitting your throat
if I thought it would get me
out of that house
a second sooner with the answers.
Duly warned.
(Both sigh)
Oh, Mother.
Your hands.
They're as beautiful
as I remembered.
What's wrong?
I have to confess something.
I killed you.
I pulled the plug on the respirator
because I couldn't bear leaving you
in that horrible nursing home.
Can you ever forgive me?
Darling,
I wanted to smother you with kisses.
I was in agony,
and you gave me peace.
- Oh.
It's beautiful here.
I feel like I can finally breathe.
MADISON: We did what you asked.
Moira's gone,
- so you can start any time now.
- Shh...
I was just savoring
the stillness.
Not only was that woman
the worst maid in God's creation,
but she would never shut up.
Death only made her more verbose.
Tell us about Michael.
Well...
he was born right here
in this house
to a mother and a family
ultimately marked for death.
(Screams)
When his mother died
pushing him out into the world,
I gladly assumed the burden
of raising him.
You see, I-I-I am a mother myself,
four times over.
- (Chuckles)
- Why you?
Because
he also happened to be my grandson.
His father was that handsome
young man in the sweater
and the mop top
that you saw when you
first came in... Tate.
Now, I am the first
to admit that, um,
there were mistakes made raising Tate.
And that's why, with Michael...
oh, my God...
he was such a perfect
little angel of light.
I thought that would be
my chance for a do-over.
You see, I was born to be a mother.
I always felt that,
to raise a great man,
that was the most admirable
and selfless act
a woman could aspire to.
He was my destiny.
Oh, such a beautiful child,
with such a cheerful disposition.
Even when he was committing
unspeakable acts.
What do you mean unspeakable?
Well, it was trivial at first,
of course, you know.
I'd find dead flies in his crib
with their wings shorn off and...
And then, as he got older...
small rodents.
I had seen enough
Discovery Channel specials
to know exactly
what evolutionary tree
he was shimmying up.
Bundy, Dahmer,
they started
with small animals, too...
until they graduated
to grander things.
He said they were presents
because he loved me.
Oh, and his love did flow.
And enjoyable as it was,
to have a child
so committed to expressing
his love for me,
I did try to encourage him
to find
another avenue of expression.
Still, nothing I could say
would get him to cease.
Each time I would dutifully
bury one of these gifts along
with a little piece of my soul.
Well, I tried to find
a silver lining
to make lemonade out of lemons,
so every time I buried
one of his presents,
I planted a rose bush on top.
You know, from death
springs life eternal.
You are childless, I presume?
A skinny little thing like you
would struggle to carry.
I don't really have
the disposition for motherhood.
If my child wasn't cool
or good-looking,
there's no way I'd love it.
Well, not me.
I loved them all.
It was Michael
who made me realize
that I was put on this earth
to raise the monsters.
I never thought I would tire
of the smell of roses.
Roses had always been
my favorite flower,
but soon they made me
just want to retch.
And of course then there was
that incident with the sitter.
I was able to convince
the authorities
that she had taken
her own life.
(Michael giggles)
At least I didn't have
to bury that one.
Um, up until that point,
I thought I was raising
a garden variety serial killer,
or possibly even a gifted one...
you know, with its
attendant challenges.
But then came the day
when he was late
getting up for school,
so I went in to wake him.
And there was a stranger
in his bed.
Well, not a stranger,
I mean, it was still my grandson.
He'd aged a decade overnight.
Now, that was something
far outside the natural realm.
It was almost as if he was
in a hurry to get somewhere,
age-wise, know what I mean?
(Choking)
You don't tell me
what to do anymore.
(Gasping)
Grandma?
(Crying) Oh.
I'm-I'm sorry.
Can I have a glass of water?
(Stammers)
M-M... May I?
M... May I?
Yes. Yes, you may.
(Crying)
When you look at men
of significance,
you know, like artists
or world leaders,
inventors, they have all had
their particular peccadilloes
on their road to the top,
haven't they?
But aging ten years
overnight...
...that called
for sacred intervention.
(Game device chiming)
I had to accept
that once again,
my days as a mother
were at an end.
I have been burdened
with heartbreak my whole life.
Broken dreams, broken promises,
broken marriages.
But this one...
(Laughs)
...this one shattered me
beyond recovery.
Michael had made me believe
that my presence here
meant something.
That I mattered.
(Sniffles)
But I was just an invisible step
along the path.
He was done with me.
Honestly, I think that...
if I had corrected his grammar
one more time,
he would've just slit my throat.
Like the help.
I wasn't going to give him
or any man the satisfaction.
I have always lived my life
on my own terms.
So I came here.
A prison, yes.
But one where I knew the rules,
and more importantly...
("You're Gonna Miss Me"
by Connie Francis playing)
...where I knew the company.
♪ One kiss ♪
♪ One little sigh ♪
Bottle of whiskey
and a fenny chaser.
(Laughs softly)
Ooh, that's what I call
a bon voyage.
♪ Someday, baby, someday, darling ♪
♪ You're gonna miss me ♪
♪ Hmm ♪
♪ Long gone ♪
♪ Is your caress ♪
♪ And with it ♪
♪ All of my happiness ♪
♪ But someday, baby ♪
♪ Someday, darling ♪
♪ You're gonna miss me ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Yes ♪
I awoke to find myself
surrounded
by my precious children.
Well, minus my beloved Addie.
God rest her soul.
But the others were there.
All of them.
With me, forever.
And that is the real reason
I bound my soul to this place.
Because, like I said earlier,
I was born to be a mother.
Why not die to be one, too?
As for my grandson...
I never wanted to see him again.
Well, there it is.
(Exhales)
The whole story.
Was it everything
you dreamed of, witchypoos?
GIRL: Mommy.
Yes, my darling?
It's almost tea time.
Of course it is,
my little beauty queen.
How foolish of me.
(Laughs softly)
Well, now.
You'll have to excuse me now.
My family calls.
Let's go.
(Moaning)
(Crying)
You gonna be much longer, DILF?
What the hell?
People don't knock anymore?
We still need to talk to you
about Michael.
BEHOLD: We're leaving
no stone unturned.
I still have nothing
to say to you. Now get out.
What if we were to fix it so you
didn't have to do that anymore?
Stand at the window, crying,
while you double-click
your mouse?
You could do that?
You can make the impulse stop?
Actually, it's only the crying
part I can live without.
The day Constance died
was when I first saw my son.
Grandma?
Grandma!
(Crying) No.
No. Hey. Hey, wake up.
Hey, wake up.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
Hey.
Grandma.
BEN: The spirits in this house
can't be seen
unless they want to be seen.
She doesn't want to see me?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Someone who wants to be seen.
Someone who wants to help.
If you really want to change,
I think I can show you how.
I'm a monster.
Why would you want to help me?
Because I can't help
but think of you as my son.
Even though you're not, really.
And so we started talking,
doctor to patient,
on that very day.
He wanted to be good,
desperately.
I could see in his eyes
how much he needed me.
I wanted him to have
all the simple joys
he never had without
a real father to show him how.
♪ To somebody new ♪
He was brilliant,
off the charts.
His brain always seemed five
steps ahead of everyone else.
♪ Although ♪
The more time I spent with him,
the more I began to feel
like a father to this boy.
♪ You're a part of my heart ♪
Everything in this house was dead.
My wife,
My baby was never going
to grow up.
Violet was never going
to get married.
But Michael was alive,
the only light
to come out of all this.
Ow.
I wanted to give him everything.
♪ It will seem once more just to ♪
What are you doing?
Stay away from my shit.
- He was just exploring.
- He's fucked-up.
You stay away from my shit,
you understand?
I just want
to be like you, Dad.
Who told you that?
Other spirits.
They whispered to me.
You didn't spring
from my nutsack, got it?
Not even I could create
something as monstrous,
as evil, as you.
You stay away from me.
BEN:
I could see him turning away.
Turning to the dark side.
And it was about to get worse.
The darkness was always
on the edges.
Encroaching.
It's impossible to avoid
in this house.
What are you doing?
Giving her a smile.
The things you have
to do to be a star.
BEN:
I was losing him.
And then the house sold.
(Engine receding)
- Ooh...
- Hey.
That's it, baby.
- We did it.
- Okay.
- Last one.
All right, here we go.
Ooh!
- (Knife slices)
- (Women screaming)
No, no, no, no!
(Panting)
Those were good people.
They deserved a chance.
They don't belong here.
Because of what you did,
they'll be here forever.
(Whimpers)
GRACE: What's happening?
I don't feel right.
You didn't have to kill them.
I know you.
This isn't who you are.
(Grace and Elizabeth screaming)
(Grunts)
I never could have helped you.
It was foolish to try.
Michael didn't just kill
those women.
He made them cease to exist.
He murdered their bodies
and then destroyed their souls.
Fuck.
So, basically, our new Supreme
is pretty much pure evil.
We should go.
Cordelia will know what to do.
How to get rid of him.
It won't be so easy.
Vivien.
Ben.
Are we speaking again?
I don't know yet.
Every haunted house
has a cold spot,
and I think we just found it.
I never stopped loving you.
I know.
But I never stopped hating him.
And I couldn't forgive you
for needing Michael.
Although, just now,
I'm starting to realize
maybe you never had a choice.
(Baby crying)
Your son needs you, Ben.
He needs his father.
(Baby continues crying)
What you're dealing with here
is not just evil.
Michael is not just a bad witch
for you to exterminate.
What is that supposed to mean?
"Then I saw a beast
with ten horns and seven heads
"rising out of the sea
and all who dwell on the Earth
will worship Him."
Nothing about Michael
is natural to me,
not his birth,
not his appearance.
I kept away from him at first
because it was painful.
And then strange things
started to happen.
A murder of crows would
encircle the house every day.
Inside it was sweltering hot.
And then they came.
(Doorbell rings)
"And the son became black
as sackcloth with hair,
"and the whole moon
became as blood...
"and the stars fell
from the Heaven to the Earth,
for the great day of wrath
is come."
(Gasps)
I am in the presence of my Lord.
Who are you?
I am Anton LaVey, Black Pope
of the Church of Satan,
and these are my cardinals.
I faked my death
to prepare for this day.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
What's going on here?
We followed a dark star
from the west.
The signs are impossible
to miss:
the temperature in this house,
a home built
over the portal to Hell,
and the crows worshipping
from above.
The omens are complete.
You're the chosen one.
The time has come to remove
the scales from your eyes,
to show you your true power.
VIVIEN:
Something changed in Michael.
It was like they opened a door
and they showed him
his true path.
Why didn't you stop them?
I think I thought it was a joke.
I mean, they were lost souls
following a con man
from some pathetic circus.
That's what it seemed like to me.
That is, until the Black Mass.
Oh, dear child,
you must be freezing.
Hop in. I'll give you a ride.
Thank you.
("(Don't Fear) The Reaper"
by Blue Oyster Cult playing)
You're a lifesaver.
I'm just a couple miles
up Riverside.
♪ They're gone ♪
♪ Seasons don't fear the reaper ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
You know something, I...
I think I'd rather walk.
It's not going to be possible.
(Whimpers)
But it's such a lovely night.
Isn't it?
For what?
Murder.
(Moaning)
(Door creaks open)
Footfalls approaching)
(Gasping)
(Chanting in foreign language)
For you, Michael.
It's all for you.
Hail Satan!
(Shouts)
(Screaming)
LaVEY: Oh! Oh!
Oh!
(Carl Orff's "O Fortuna" playing)
Ave Satanas.
Father.
I am with you now.
VIVIEN: That night
was a terrible storm.
Hail as big as rocks,
rain of blood.
It was then that I made
the decision to kill him.
(Vivien screams)
Tate saved me.
And after we put the fire out,
Michael was gone.
I don't know where he went.
I don't know who raised him
after he left.
The only thing I know is, Ben
is not his father, nor is Tate.
He was born from the evil
of this house.
The source of darkness
is his true father,
and he is here
to destroy the world.
BEHOLD: Madison.
Madison.
Look, I know it sucks
that the guy you put
your hopes into
turned out to be the Antichrist,
but you are not stopping me
from telling the council.
I wasn't gonna stop you.
I never would have fought
for Michael to be Supreme
if I had any idea
about who he truly is.
We just wanted a leader.
But he is clearly not that.
What if we can't stop him?
What happens then?
I don't know.
(Soft crying)
(Crying)
Give me a second.
If you want to ask me about
Michael, I can't help you.
I stayed clear of him.
Probably a good call.
I think we got enough
on him anyway.
Then what do you want?
Seems like you're having
a hard time.
You and that Tate guy have
a real angsty thing going on.
We don't have anything.
We can't.
He's a monster.
He didn't seem
like a monster to me.
You don't know him.
You can't imagine what it's like
to know all of the horrible
things he's done.
And still be in love with him?
It's torture... every day.
I've done some bad things I'm
not exactly proud of in my life
and my second life.
But those were my choices.
I think what happened to Tate
was different.
He wasn't the real evil here.
What does that even mean?
It's like this house
used him as a vessel
to create something
way, way worse.
My guess... any evil inside Tate
left with Michael.
It would be nice if that were true.
Maybe you just need to see
the truth for yourself.
Tate?
You saved my mom.
I'm so sorry for everything. I...
I know.
("Spirits in the Material World"
by The Police playing)
♪ There is no political solution ♪
♪ To our troubled evolution ♪
You're really nothing
but a softie, aren't you?
Whatever.
I just thought I'd help
two ghosts get laid.
At least someone's gonna get
a happy ever after.
There's not gonna be
an ever after for anyone
if we don't find a way
to stop Michael.
♪ We are spirits in the material world ♪
♪ Are spirits in the material world ♪